tfaforms.net 2019-09-15

# Privacy Policy - FormAssembly

### Effective Date: February 28, 2017

The FormAssembly Inc. Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality services with integrity in dealing with our Users and Subscribers. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be assessed from time to time against new technologies, business practices and our Subscribers and their Users’ needs. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged FormAssembly Inc.

* * *

### Definitions

Subscribers
    “Subscribers” are individuals or entities who use this site for free or for charge to create forms and surveys for use with their businesses.
Users
    “Users” are customers and other invitees of a Subscriber who access such forms and voluntarily input data into the form as requested by the Subscriber.

* * *

### EU–U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss – US Privacy Shield Framework

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, FormAssembly Inc. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact FormAssembly Inc. at: [contact@formassembly.com](mailto:contact@formassembly.com).

FormAssembly Inc. commits to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU and Switzerland in the context of the employment relationship.

An organization must offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt out) whether their personal information is (i) to be disclosed to a third party or (ii) to be used for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individuals. Individuals must be provided with clear, conspicuous, and readily available mechanisms to exercise choice.

FormAssembly Inc. complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss – U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. FormAssembly Inc. has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

FormAssembly Inc. is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. FormAssembly Inc. complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, FormAssembly Inc. is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, FormAssembly Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

* * *

## What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our Web site [www.formassembly.com](https://www.formassembly.com/) you may provide two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

### 1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

If you choose to subscribe to our services, we collect personal information such as: Name, Email Address, Mailing Address and Credit Card Information.

When a User completes a form created, or purchased, by one of our Subscribers, the User may choose to provide the Subscriber with personal information, such as:

Name  
Mailing address  
E-mail address  
Social security number  
Health related information  
Home and business phone number  
Other personal information (i.e., mother’s maiden name)  
E-mail Information

We ask that Subscribers who create forms on our Site do not use the forms to collect credit card information. However, WE ARE NOT ABLE TO MONITOR OR RESTRICT ALL OF THE INFORMATION REQUESTED BY OUR SUBSCRIBERS. FURTHER, DESPITE OUR EFFORTS TO PROTECT INFORMATION, WE DO NOT GUARANTEE THAT ALL INFORMATION THAT IS PROVIDED WILL REMAIN SECURE. See the section titled ‘How Can Your Information be Secured?’ below for further information.

FormAssembly Inc. collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. FormAssembly Inc. works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected.

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly. If you are a Client and would like to update your account please [contact us here](https://www.formassembly.com/contact.php).

In addition to providing the foregoing information to our Subscribers, if you choose to correspond further through e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

### 2\. Web Site Use Information

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

* * *

## How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we may use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities and for providing Subscriber service. We are a Web site host and our primary function as it relates to User data is to facilitate use of the forms and to store such User inputted data for use by the Subscriber for their business purposes. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. WE DO NOT SELL OR SHARE ANY COLLECTED INFORMATION WITH ANY THIRD PARTY OTHER THAN THE SUBSCRIBER TO WHOM YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE INFORMATION TO. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR HOW THE SUBSCRIBER USES THE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY USERS. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, [contact us here](https://www.formassembly.com/contact.php).

We do not spam email and we do not permit our Subscribers to spam to the extent we can reasonably prevent such efforts. Our Terms of Service prohibit all Subscribers from engaging in spam activity. Violations of this policy may result in immediate termination of service and legal action.

### Subscriber Credit Card Information

For subscribers, any Credit Card information collected by FormAssembly is used for the following general purposes:

  1. Product and services provisioning;
  2. Billing; and,
  3. Identification and authentication.

Subscriber Credit Card information is processed and stored by a third-party payment provider, Stripe, Inc., (“Stripe”) a certified PCI Level 1 Service Provider. Stripe will never provide your card information to FormAssembly. Stripe will share contact information to FormAssembly to enable FormAssembly to deliver product and services provisioning. Stripe will not share Subscriber information with third-parties unless Subscriber authorizes Stripe to do so. For more information, please review Stripe’s Privacy Policy (<https://stripe.com/us/privacy>).

FormAssembly Inc. may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients.

* * *

### Choice/Opt-Out

We enable you to create an account, and share information such as messages, offers, & requests with others.

**Newsletters & Promotional Emails**  
As part of our service, you have the option to receive our newsletter. Out of respect for your privacy, if you wish to no longer receive our newsletters you may follow the instructions in the email and/or make the appropriate setting changes directly in your account.

**Service-related Announcements**  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. These emails are service related and not marketing/promotional in nature therefore you might not be able to opt-out.

**Surveys or Contests**  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to gather feedback on new or improved features, determine what improvements should be made to the application, and improve personalization of the application. In the case of a contest, information is used to notify winners and award prizes.

**Blog and Forum**  
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. _To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at_ [contact@formassembly.com](mailto:contact@formassembly.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Our blog is also managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

* * *

## Tracking Technologies

We FormAssembly Inc. and our partners use technologies such as cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

To manage Flash cookies, please click here: [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)

We use cookies to remember users’ settings (e.g., language preference) and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party to manage our advertising of our service on other sites. We use retargeting to advertise our product. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. Please note, you may opt-out of all activity-based ads, from us and others, by clicking [here](https://preferences.truste.com/here) (or if located in the European Union [click here](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

* * *

## How Can Your Information be Secured?

We provide the capability for your data to be encrypted. However, the creator of the form in which you input data chooses how and whether to encrypt your information. Before inputting any sensitive information, determine if encryption is enabled by looking for the “lock” symbol on your web browser or a yellow highlight in the web browser address bar.

INFORMATION OR E-MAIL THAT YOU SEND TO US MAY NOT BE SECURE UNLESS WE ADVISE YOU THAT SECURITY MEASURES WILL BE IN PLACE PRIOR TO YOUR TRANSMITTING THE INFORMATION. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as a social security number to us through an unsecured e-mail.

* * *

## Information Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at contact@formassembly.com. We do not, however, secure your personal information that is in the possession or control of our Subscriber.

* * *

## How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

FormAssembly Inc. has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, who seeks to correct, amend, delete inaccurate data or withdraw consent to further contact should direct his/her query to FormAssembly Inc.‘s Client (the data controller). If the Client requests FormAssembly Inc. to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days.

Upon request FormAssembly Inc. will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may request access to all your personally identifiable information to correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by making the change by logging into your account, by emailing us at contact@formassembly.com, or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. FormAssembly Inc. will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

* * *

## What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?

In certain situations, FormAssembly Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process,
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if FormAssembly Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

* * *

## What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

Integration with 3rd party services (Google Apps, Salesforce and more) requires exchange of information, such as credentials (username, password, open ID/single-sign-on tokens) and any other data required for implementation of said integration. Integration is optional, and subscribers must explicitly authorize such transaction. Any data received from 3rd party service is covered by this privacy policy.

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site (such as our blog) nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the Users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link to our Web site, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

Although not owned, controlled, or moderated by our site, we do offer a link to our publicly accessible customer feedback tool. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

* * *

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Follow us on Twitter button [and Widgets, such as Google Plus button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

* * *

## Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Your continued or subsequent use of our services after any such change shall constitute your consent to such change.

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at contact@formassembly.com.

* * *

## Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

* * *

## Questions & Privacy Dispute Resolution

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us by email at: contact@formassembly.com,  
by phone: (844) 293-2367, or by post mail at:

`FormAssembly Inc.  
885 S College Mall Rd, #399  
Bloomington, IN 47401  
`
